https://www.flumelaw.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAttorney ProfileFirm OverviewBankruptcy Information CenterBankruptcy Lawyer Rick FlumeGeneral InformationChapter 7 BankruptcyChapter 13 BankruptcyCircumstances Of People Filing BankruptcyTypes of People Filing For BankruptcyAlternatives To BankruptcyHow Bankruptcy Affects Your Credit?What Are The Benefits Of Bankruptcy?Process of BankruptcyAssets Management During and After BankruptcyWho Is Involved When Someone Files For Bankruptcy?What Can A Person Keep When They File For Bankruptcy?Bankruptcy Warning SignsHow An Automatic Stay Works?Texas Bankruptcy TimelineWhat Is The Means Test & How Does It Work?Useful TipsLife After BankruptcyBankruptcy Is AffordableIs Bankruptcy The Best Option?Bankruptcy And Your CreditThree-Step Debt ReliefMistakes To Avoid In BankruptcyLife After BankruptcyYou Deserve A Fresh StartSuffering From Creditor Harassment?Various Bankruptcy Myths341 Meeting of CreditorsWhat Is The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Would Both Spouses Have To Attend The 341 Meeting If They Filed Together?Clients Concern In Meeting Of CreditorsWhat Happens During The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Can The Person Talk To Their Attorney During The Meeting?Hiring An AttorneyHiring Bankruptcy LawyerWhy Do You Need An Attorney?San Antonio Bankruptcy LawyerBankrupty Legal Guide On AVVOFAQsGeneral Bankruptcy FAQsAVVO AnswersTestimonialsCase EvaluationContact Us
FILL OUT A FREECASE EVALUATION
FREE CONSULTATION 210-930-7000HomeAttorney ProfileFirm OverviewBankruptcy Information CenterBankruptcy Lawyer Rick FlumeGeneral InformationChapter 7 BankruptcyChapter 13 BankruptcyCircumstances Of People Filing BankruptcyTypes of People Filing For BankruptcyAlternatives To BankruptcyHow Bankruptcy Affects Your Credit?What Are The Benefits Of Bankruptcy?Process of BankruptcyAssets Management During and After BankruptcyWho Is Involved When Someone Files For Bankruptcy?What Can A Person Keep When They File For Bankruptcy?Bankruptcy Warning SignsHow An Automatic Stay Works?Texas Bankruptcy TimelineWhat Is The Means Test & How Does It Work?Useful TipsLife After BankruptcyBankruptcy Is AffordableIs Bankruptcy The Best Option?Bankruptcy And Your CreditThree-Step Debt ReliefMistakes To Avoid In BankruptcyLife After BankruptcyYou Deserve A Fresh StartSuffering From Creditor Harassment?Various Bankruptcy Myths341 Meeting of CreditorsWhat Happens During The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?What Is The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Would Both Spouses Have To Attend The 341 Meeting If They Filed Together?Clients Concern In Meeting Of CreditorsWhat Happens During The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Can The Person Talk To Their Attorney During The Meeting?Bankruptcy Mistakes To AvoidYou’ve Been Sued! What Next?Hiring An AttorneyHiring Bankruptcy LawyerWhy Do You Need An Attorney?San Antonio Bankruptcy LawyerBankrupty Legal Guide On AVVOFAQsGeneral Bankruptcy FAQsAVVO AnswersTestimonialsVideosCase EvaluationContact Us×HomeAttorney ProfileFirm OverviewBankruptcy Information CenterBankruptcy Lawyer Rick FlumeGeneral InformationChapter 7 BankruptcyChapter 13 BankruptcyCircumstances Of People Filing BankruptcyTypes of People Filing For BankruptcyAlternatives To BankruptcyHow Bankruptcy Affects Your Credit?What Are The Benefits Of Bankruptcy?Process of BankruptcyAssets Management During and After BankruptcyWho Is Involved When Someone Files For Bankruptcy?What Can A Person Keep When They File For Bankruptcy?Bankruptcy Warning SignsHow An Automatic Stay Works?Texas Bankruptcy TimelineWhat Is The Means Test & How Does It Work?Useful TipsLife After BankruptcyBankruptcy Is AffordableIs Bankruptcy The Best Option?Bankruptcy And Your CreditThree-Step Debt ReliefMistakes To Avoid In BankruptcyLife After BankruptcyYou Deserve A Fresh StartSuffering From Creditor Harassment?Various Bankruptcy Myths341 Meeting of CreditorsWhat Is The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Would Both Spouses Have To Attend The 341 Meeting If They Filed Together?Clients Concern In Meeting Of CreditorsWhat Happens During The 341 Meeting Of Creditors?Can The Person Talk To Their Attorney During The Meeting?Hiring An AttorneyHiring Bankruptcy LawyerWhy Do You Need An Attorney?San Antonio Bankruptcy LawyerBankrupty Legal Guide On AVVOFAQsGeneral Bankruptcy FAQsAVVO AnswersTestimonialsCase EvaluationContact UsDue to social distancing guidelines, all consultations are conducted by phone or teleconference, like Zoom, and all paperwork is handled by email or fax.This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Rick Flume, Bankruptcy Attorney relating to www.flumelaw.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.Sharing We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & Contests From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 210-930-7000 or via mail Attn: Privacy Policy, 900 NE Loop 410, Suite E-105, San Antonio, TX 78209.CALL US NOW(210) 930-7000Get your Free copy of the best selling book Bankruptcy Made Simple To Understand Click Here to OrderAttorney Rick FlumeOver 14 Years of Legal ExperienceVast experience in solving bankruptcy related issuesDevoted To Protect The Rights Of His ClientsMemberNational Association of Consumer Bankruptcy Attorneys (NACBA)State Bar of TexasSan Antonio Bar AssociationSan Antonio Bankruptcy Bar AssociationRecent Posts Will I Qualify For Chapter 7 Bankruptcy? Factors That Determine The Appropriate Income To Compare To Median Income Advantages of a Chapter 7 Over a Chapter 13 Factors That Help Determine Appropriate Household Size Use A Tax Refund To Buy A Cash Car?Schedule yourFree ConsultationRecent Posts Will I Qualify For Chapter 7 Bankruptcy?Here’s the “Easy” button: For the typical person that I see in a debt consultation, the determining factors for qualification for a Chapter 7 bankruptcy are the person’s income and expenses. Keep in mind, it’s like looking at an elephant… Factors That Determine The Appropriate Income To Compare To Median IncomeOne factor in determining if you qualify for Chapter 7 is to compare your previous six months of income to median income for people in Texas, based on the household size. Although you can be above median income and still… Advantages of a Chapter 7 Over a Chapter 13Most people that file bankruptcy file under Chapter 7, which is the form of bankruptcy where there is no monthly payment to a trustee. Chapter 7 has numerous advantages over Chapter 13. Here are the key advantages: Chapter 7 Bankruptcy… View All »CALL FOR YOUR FREE CONSULTATION! | (210) 930-7000The information on this website is for general information purposes only. Nothing on this site should be taken aslegal advice for any individual case or situation. This information is not intended to create, and receipt or viewingdoes not constitute, an attorney-client relationship.We are a debt relief agency. We help people file for bankruptcy relief under the Bankruptcy Code.HomeBlogGlossaryTerms Of UsePrivacy PolicyContact UsCopyright © 2020 Rick Flume, Bankruptcy Attorney. All Rights Reserved.
Powered By
xFREE Case Evaluation
